WARNING
IT FELT SO UNFAIR.
ONE FLEETING MOMENT, AND MISFORTUNE
SWALLOWED ME WHOLE.
YET, AGAIN AND AGAIN…
HUU
...I'M MADE TO FEEL AS IF I WAS BORN ONLY
TO SUFFER.
HAA...
HAA…
...THE WIND STIRS...
...THE FLOWERS BLOOM...
...MIGHT BE NOTHING MORE THAN RUINS.
Dirty Deeds
MAKE SURE EVERYTHING'S READY.
DING-A-LING
MS. CHEON'S USUALLY THE ONE TENDING
YEONGHWADANG...
WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT SHE WOULD FALL SICK
TODAY OF ALL DAYS?
CLACK
IT'S BEEN WHAT, NINE YEARS SINCE THIS
ANNEX WAS LAST USED?
JUST A WEEK AGO, THIS WAS STILL MY STUDIO.
SIT
THERE'S STILL SOME TIME BEFORE NIGHTFALL.
LONG TIME NO SEE, MAN!
YEAH, IT'S BEEN A WHILE. CAME TO SEE YOUR
PARENTS, HUH?
THE WHOLE MARRIAGE TALK IS KILLING ME.
ME?
I WAS SUPPOSED TO TELL YOU THIS...
I might...
WAIT, YOU'RE DATING THAT SAHUI YEON?!
NOT EXACTLY DATING...
SHE STILL STUPIDLY HOT OR WHAT?
OBVIOUS?
SHE'S DAMAGED GOODS, AFTER ALL.
SERIOUSLY, WHAT ELSE DOES SHE HAVE?
DOES SHE HAVE BESIDES HER BODY?
WHY AM I EVEN LISTENING TO THIS GARBAGE?
LIMP
I'D BETTER CLOSE IT OFF MYSELF.
...ARRIVES.
BUT YOU THINK YOU COULD EVEN SLEEP WITH
HER?
ISN'T SHE, LIKE, PARALYZED FROM THE WAIST
DOWN?
THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT? IT'S JUST
HER ANKLE. THE REST WORKS FINE.
OH?
DAMN, I'M JEALOUS, MAN! SHE'S GOT A GREAT
RACK.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW HOW IT IS AFTER I TRY
HER OUT.